joinindiannavy.gov.in 2019-02-27

# Privacy Policy - Join Indian Navy | Government of India

We do not collect personal Information for any purpose other than to respond to you. If you choose to provide us with personal information like when filling out a 'Contact Us' with an e-mail address or postal address, and submit it to us through the website, we may use that information to respond to your message, and to give you the information sought.

  * We do not create individual profiles for commercial marketing. While you must provide an email address for a localized response to you query or comments forwarded to us, we recommend that you do not include any other personal information unless specifically asked to.
  * If we seek any other personal information, you would be informed about its intended use. If, at any time you believe the principle referred to in this privacy statement has not been followed, or have any other comments on these principles, please notify the concerned authority through the ‘contact us’ page of IN-Website and we shall proceed for resolution of conflict, if any.
  * The use of terms “Personal Information” in this privacy statement refers to any information through which your identify gets apparent or can be reasonably ascertained.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of software code that the website, being accessed, sends to the browser, accessing the website. By making use of a similar technology, our website too sends cookies to the browser of the user, accessing website, for increasing the access-speed but we do not gather user information of any kind during the process.
